[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "Which of the choices below is used in the article as an example of a business that IS sustainable?",
        "answer": "a company that takes plastic waste and makes it into usable products"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, allowing all types of workers to be hired in a company is considered:",
        "answer": "inclusive"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, full employment means____, and productive employment means _____.",
        "answer": "almost everyone who wants to work can get a job ... jobs pay a living wage"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, which of the following is closest in meaning to “...create work that is good for the environment, allows all types of workers, and helps the towns where the work takes place.”",
        "answer": "promote sustained, inclusive and sustainable growth"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is closest in meaning to allow workers to express their concerns?",
        "answer": "let workers talk about work problems"
    },
    {
        "question": "The article mentions living wages. Which of the following is closest to living wages?",
        "answer": "The income necessary for workers to meet their basic needs."
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, which of the following situations would be considered full employment?",
        "answer": "98 out of 100 people looking for work would be able to find a job"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, inclusive means _____, and sustainable means _____.",
        "answer": "companies will hire all members of a society ... the work will not harm, and possibly even help, the environment over time"
    },
    {
        "question": "The article mentions the word disabilities. Which of the following words is an example of a disability?",
        "answer": "blindness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, what is the percentage of workers who are not paid enough to pay for basic food, clothing, or shelter?",
        "answer": "eight percent"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year did the United Nations agree to the Agenda for Sustainable growth?",
        "answer": "2015"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the choices below is used in the article as an example of an industry that is NOT sustainable?",
        "answer": "coal mining"
    },
    {
        "question": "The article mentions “allow workers to express their concerns”. Which of the following is closest in meaning to express?",
        "answer": "discuss work-related issues with the company’s managers and the public"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many goals are in the United Nations Agenda for Sustainable Development?",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT mentioned as an example of decent work?",
        "answer": "annual bonuses"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on what you’ve learned from the article, which of the following is most correct?",
        "answer": "If you don’t understand a long or complicated sentence, try breaking it into smaller pieces to understand smaller pieces, and then putting all the pieces together again."
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on what you’ve read in the article, which of the following is NOT correct?",
        "answer": "The United Nations has a plan called “The 2040 Agenda for Sustainable Development.”\n\nCoal mining is not a sustainable industry."
    }
]